<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Niek Beckers</title>
    <link>https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Niek Beckers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 21:25:55 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JOAN: a framework for human-automated vehicle experiments</title>
      <link>https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/joan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 21:25:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/joan/</guid>
      <description>The Human-Robot Interaction group of Cognitive Robotics at TU Delft does a lot of research on interactions between humans and automated vehicles (drivers, but also pedestrians and other road users). In order to facilitate this research, we need a high-fidelity and customizable virtual reality driving simulator.
At the core of our virtual driving simulator is CARLA, a driving simulator based on the Unreal gaming engine developed for autonomous vehicle-related research CARLA has been developed to support the development, training, and validation of autonomous vehicles, and contains a massive toolset for machine learning applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS: the Bi-RObot Setup</title>
      <link>https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niekbeckers.github.io/projects/bros/</guid>
      <description>During my PhD I studied and modeled how two people perform a task together through physical interaction: by interacting through forces for which I used a robot setup. Together with Koen from Hankamp Rehab, we designed and built our own robotic setup to perform my experiments. The setup consists of two identical high-performance planar robots, controlled by a real-time operating system (through EtherCAT and TwinCAT). We did multiple experiments on them, with over 140 participants and multiple Master theses 😃.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
